The Star Wars prequels: Pretty damn hated back in the day, but these days a lot of people like them...
Ironically. The best way to like something. But are the prequels actually good?
EHHHHHHHH....
Killian, do you love Star Wars?
No, I'm a Star Wars fan. I'm willing to go as far as we are acquaintances.
I acquaintance Star Wars. A long time ago
There was a story about a captured princess
who sent a message to an old warrior of a magic order yet instead,
the message went to a young farm boy who lived with his uncle.
That was the story of
Eragon, a ripoff of Star Wars!
a trilogy that ended in '83. 10 years later, creator George Lucas
announced that he was making a prequel trilogy with Evan McGregor cast as
Obi-Wan Kenobi, plus other actors, you might not notice them but but they're...they are there.
Using the revolutionary technology named CGI, they could make more toy ads-
I mean, fascinating aliens than ever before. The first film of the new trilogy came out in '99
and everyone loved it...
in my age group.
Adults though, that they had a couple of complaints.
Star Wars the very real menace
Every joke about prequels has been made. So I'm sorry if something sounds familiar
Anyways, the Phantom Menace was the biggest disappointment since my son
He's a Nobel Prize winning astronaut that plays for Real Madrid
So it's not really disappointment to me much like the Phantom Menace. I had no expectations
I didn't know what Star Wars was before this film but most haters disliked it from
Turmoil has engulfed the Galactic Republic the taxation that right there
that's when people started dislike it the films about a straight Federation that are angry at a republic and are currently
Blockading a planet with warships, which is legal Wow. What's a weak legislative body?
I sure hope someone doesn't abuse that fact
Republic sent two Jedi to solve this qui-gon jinn and obi-wan
and they tried to kill them in the trade Federation's defense if the UN settles a trade dispute and their
Negotiators are Navy SEAL Mormons might send mixed messages
They actually attack because the Trade Federation is run by Darth Sidious
Who is that? Well, he was a scheming bad guy
now I
Don't know anymore. See this is like in babe. Nabela. Would the sinneth find that illegal?
Why would I oh oh you mean who cares just do it?
The Jedi joined the invading force and rescues fuck who can do a five-meter jump
This is very important. He takes you to to the High Council of the displaced natives the Gungans
It's only one species is allowed to speak
Apart fish state the robots above will attack you Gungans. No dice electric. We saw underwater
Stupid have a ding-ding go get eaten by fish with a very specific face limit know
Georgia be executed
Ah, they bring him along gotta entertain kids and set up that twist in next one good news, though
They don't get it son. He was wrong. There was always a bigger fish
Maybe he's wrong about the droids feed city
Rescue the Queen Portman in distress. Let's get this Queen pads made to the galaxy's capital croissant
But she's like no, I got a stick by and die for my people
mmm
Croissant. Yeah sure. Let's go and they get killed by artillery fire. What a realistic end to a movie about war
No, they get saved by a droid and they spend a lot of time on this droid
It's a smart borscht screwdriver who cares to repair the ship
They have to travel to fan service, which is nearby
And considering its space. I'm guessing nearby means a couple of thousands of years of travel
Meanwhile Trade Federation lets me teach you trade check out this toy seller
jealous on sand planets only one guy has the parts according to himself and
Qui-gon believes him. He also has a slave. My name is Anakin Skywalker. That's not a surname
I stole to look cool again with the toys my god. Are you a Jedi Knight?
I'm a Jedi Master you little shit. You wouldn't ask a doctor if he's in high school. Did you come to free the slaves?
I look like Jesus not Moses you are on your own yet qui-gon senses something weird about a child
It's like his in a school play and is acting
permanently
So he analyzes his midi-chlorian count and it's the highest ever midi-chlorians are
microscopic life-forms that give people access to the force much like how a good immune system gives you access to
springtime qui-gon believes
midi-chlorians banged the Anakin's mom
No sex education in Jedi temples the Jedi also do not forbid
Gambling so he bets the child on a race that leader. Imagine how much fun this must be for sandpeople
That man had a family
This is the first time Anakin attempted to kill a person he gets better at it now
He can become a space samurai
But he doesn't want things to change and now his mom says you can't stop change anymore
You can stop the Sun from setting
Years later and it would stop the Sun from setting your fault then an important thing gets removed
So this part makes no sense a SIF named no character yet attacks and qui-gon gone away
She'll try to burn him with the ships engine they land on Coruscant the capital of the galaxy
Who is that? Friendly gentleman, he looks like a nice kayak instructor
Hello, Senator, Palpatine. How do we stop our population getting slaughtered? Hello your majesty. Let me be frank
I thought you were Shiva. Yeah
Sheiva franked the Senate Palpatine Sidious, but honestly, the current counselor is a human pork
Let's betray him now. Yes. Okay counselor the Naboo believes. He pees sitting down vote of no-confidence
Everyone agrees now, he would definitely be impeached I swear this time
He'll be impeached promise this time. Meanwhile, Annie is getting interviewed by the Jedi Council, but they find him
afraid
Anakin is like yeah, my mother was left with a slave trader. He just lost all his money up a bit worried. Hmm
What a coward you are. They tell coy gone
We will not train him because Anakin is a chicken cuckoo cuckoo cuckoo
Are you doing chicken noises out of order?
I would still train this boy and let me tell you if he tried to stop me
I have a very specific set of skills while qui-gon is threatening Jerrold poof on this company
Georgia is like hey Quinn, you know Xhosa have an army
We sure do huge gangin military lobbies corrupt our system. Sounds killed
Let's go to Naboo and kick some robot arse. So they all go back to Naboo. Hello
I am actually the princess fake green man. You look like a typical dictator. I will stroke your ego
Will you let your people die for me he agrees?
They aren't even his species who cares he cares
So little he makes George or general as a joke when this Nimbus or worse
He also bought this in the gnome cannon fodder argan attacked Naboo palace to kidnap the visor of companies
They reach the palace and wait
Sight it's what happened. Where's John John get in here right now. We need you to save this movie one track. Oh, thank god
He's here
Motto
When this came out lots of people complained about that they don't care about the characters so it doesn't matter
Here's the thing though after movies game series and other stuff I do care about these characters. Yes
I care even more about these pillars
they are plasma generators waster power plant inside royal palace Naboo spent a fortune on
Architects and like 16 credits on the city planner Liam. No
It's overall v1. I had high ground. Mr. Moore. That's not ground
That's floor what mall was cotton enough because there's no seat library. Therefore no dictionaries
Canon, the kid blows up and saves today, but it's so dumb
I was gonna ignore it then the actor was brutally harassed and so was the charger actor
Fortunately obsessive Star Wars fans, never harassed another actor again when it came out. I liked it to be fair
It was the third non cartoon movie I had ever seen
After text driver and race read I didn't think the dialogue was bad because I couldn't understand it and I could not read
Critics at the time. I thought it was mediocre their biggest complaint not enough Kit Fisto
Is I'm not a single person complained about too much CGI because they did not know the word CGI yet
They called it. I can be like the filthy caveman
They are they also complained about the dialogue when George saw the reviews. He said oh
You think that's bad dialogue Star Wars?
Defense of the clones the other side started it
thousands of star
Systems have said we out and the Jedi are not paid enough to deal with this
So it's time to vote for a Republican a the film begins with someone trying to kill senator
Padme admit Allah too lazy to stay monarch, huh to protect her
She says obi-wan should protect her cut - obi-wan and god damn
George must have given that kid bull semen to grow so much in two years. We are now introduced to the big problem with this
Anything and the King says ever maybe it's intentional. He is an awkward religious teenager
Maybe it's intentional Lucas is sadist. Anyways, I hate it that night attempt
number two on padmé's life, but they stopped it last second and
Good thing Obi knows the film's age rating is 12
He would be bleeding all over they chased the assassin say no to drugs catch her and she dies
Which is lucky this one Dart fucks up the entire
separatist movement bill Jedi Council with Ireland KITT bad movie
ok bounty hunter needs to be found Padme needs protection mace winks to Broda and is like
Obi-wan you find the bounty hunter and will pair up your horny pad one with the hot senator
Winner, son of a bitch you are I mean wise idea Annie and Palpatine has a relationship do you think sheeps card?
Think he's a sugar daddy
I've talked too much
Anakin makes Pat me uncomfortable and then they leave for their romantic getaway obi-wan heads to an American diner in
space the space American says the arrow comes from Kamino a
Cloning planet isn't cloning essentially slavery
No, it's essentially file-sharing of humans. But Camino is not in the Jedi archives. So we asked the
Forgot his name his friends with Gerald poof and Kit Fisto
Well, well, he's got nothing. So he asks the kids and he points out some boomer might have pressed the delete button
meanwhile on Naboo
Remember back when I said the Romans dialogue is awkward
I was a jealous beta back then it would so work prepare to be Annie peeled step 1 pick up line
I don't like sound chicks take that if you say something I don't like something you like
If you say I don't like something you dislike iced Esprit trying too hard
I dislikes and this guy is interesting. And yes
Interesting opinions other things chicks like Porsche riding and posting on social media about body positivity
Right body positive forces finally chicks don't like fake magic, but they love real magic
It's forbidden fruit for them because if they do which we burn them do these three things and you'll get all the girls
Now we can finally go back to the interesting plot. Obi-wan finds Kamino
He's immediately introduced the prime minister tells him
So yeah, Jedi Master came here and ordered a million clones
We built an army for you. And I love how old ones just displace along. Yes. I knew about that
He he did prepay right look at them
Beautiful. Did they just park the clones there?
If they don't get to fight to what wait a minute tall live on top of oceans
Space Dutch that would explain why all the clones have New Zealand accents they are from old
Zealand and the clones are New Zealanders
Canon Benny's introduced Jango Fett's I was recruited by dark tyrannies a not Troy to kill Padme. Okay. Nice meeting you
On the boo man is having nightmares about his mother she in danger step for sure you care about family
she'll join you to your home planet his former slave owner sold this month to a
Single man who married her that's not great
Different culture different culture don't pissing phobic off to the Lars family farm loss. That's not a surname
dumped at weenie
Your mother has been kidnapped by sand people okay time for any to use his number-one skill murder
Obi-wan followed mr. Face to Genesis the bounty hunter drops amazing sound bombs
Hoping Obi will slow down to appreciate the sound but using unbelievable Jedi focus obi-wan ignores them
There are a lot of massive warships on this planet turns out they're producing army
Oh be found two army productions in one day if he finds a third
He'll win ajeeb can't talk is here and he's talking to some lobbies if they wanna do some war profiteering. Everyone is down
Let's invade Republic technology Union dropped the fastest beats and he finds his mother and she dies in his arm
Should have brought some med packs
Terrible timing man, then he goes for a massive KD score and he doesn't only kill the sand children
But also the sand ants and the sand cousins
hmm in terrible pain young Skywalker is obviously not as much pain as the sand people but
Psychological pain then he returns. Hey Padme. I killed children, and I enjoyed it. So Padme quickly runs away
Padme no
No
No what Fatma should have done you did the right thing I have to go now and not contact the Jedi cancelled
Have you exiled while he was having his physical therapy Obi sent a message?
We find out the big baddest Count Dooku. Here's the thing
There is a theory that the big bad was actually supposed to be Jar Jar Binks Darth Jar Jar
But I don't feel like explaining it to you. So I'm gonna report it as fact
This was actually supposed to be Jar Jar and Darth Jar. Jar gives the councilor more emergency powers to create an army
Ducotel, so be a Sith Lord named the Senate rules the Senate onion Padme traveled to Genesis to rescue will be imaged
Captured. Yeah, that's what we expected now. They will be eaten by monsters
ancient Roman entertainments
We really need to bring this back can probably make a lot of money through streaming services
Monsters can't compete with plot armor
Also, there was a bunch of jeddah is in the audience and none of the bugs noticed them see what you want machine oceans
They aren't racist
Jango and Mays face each other are and boba watches are now the Jedi loose
What?
Useless the separatists are right are ya very lucky army. This is all I love that front
So the Republic can't get anything done on normal day, but when it comes to amassing an army
They can do it in an hour
What the hell so Duke who runs and the Jew will follow and they have no teamwork and he stops at time paradox
Count Dooku, you're not dealing with the average Jedi warrior
That's how Anakin lost his arm. Hey that guy
Damn it. Is this the same species as baby Yoda. Is this your doll?
Whatever he breaks Saruman's heinie
But he escapes it ends with the two of them getting married Padme in a life of politics
Can't detect red flags now the Clone Wars
begins on one side clones led by sheev, Palpatine
On the other side droids led by savino Palpatine. Oh, but what happens during the war Star Wars?
The Clone Wars way sort of war but clones shouldn't it be like the Civil War or the war for separatists independence?
I grew up with 2d Clone Wars and it was epic beyond everything made by Samurai Jack man
It had a new character
General Grievous who was a super epic bad as Jedi killer is what George told the animators
Then it changed his mind to a guy with asthma mace windu beats up 1000 Androids by hand
It was so badass Disney declared it - epic - cannon in
2008 Oh George made a clone wars 3d movie in it Anakin gets an apprentice named artichoke
Anakin doesn't want one but she's impulsive might I get the counsel of his back. She doesn't die yet
The film was a pilot episode for the series that I'm sure a lot of my younger viewers grew up with
I started watched it while I was making this video and it's pretty damn brutal
People die left and right some are tortured to death
It's a pretty great time and an excellent way to introduce kids to war
currently on its final season leading into Burn Notice
si and
Boy, is it a revenge god? Damn?
the third film in trilogy is way better than the others in every way it begins after the Battle of
We're General Grievous risked a large portion of his army to kidnap one politician
extremely high-risk extremely low reward and the anobii reached
Grievous's ship and way to become Dooku is also here
So both commanders joined the battle and around the same symp you're almost as incompetent as the first order they battle obi-wan
clearly skipped breakfast
but Anakin had oatmeal with pumpkin seeds and to drink a large glass of the
Darkside uses that to defeat Dooku Palpatine says do it
No, don't he has a lots of information. You've captured Heinrich time to interrogate him
It wasn't a Jedi way. I've seen the Clone Wars. You've killed like a hundred people
Let's kill obi-wan - right then the clones start bombing the ship the counselors on the clones are
100% trained to save the Republic even if it is by mistake, they get captured and taken to Grievous
General Grievous you seem to have a disease that if I mention it will really do
They fight, but instead look at this guy he will mention this work environment to HR hike it's Grievous all hot and sweaty
So to get some fresh air he opens the window escapes and is laughing to himself. What's a coping mechanism?
I'm pretty sure this was the greatest military disaster in Star Wars history the ship crashes at a convenient
Runway Annie meets up with his wife that the two of them are together is probably the worst kept secret on the planet
Padme reveals that she is pregnant
Anakin doesn't know how to react because he does not know how it works
Meanwhile, Grievous is landing on another planet contacts dark Sidious about to COO
He doesn't care because he's getting a new younger apprentice
Who could it be? Let's use the clues someone younger than Christopher Lee it could be
Everyone except Jodha back at Capitol
So enough no
No, it's because I'm so pleased
Jesus come back to stop this when Anakin sleeping the force sends him a vision of
Padme seeing the flirting earlier why imagine being an ancient galactic energy?
You cannot drive people to do crazy stuff for entertainment
He decides to ask you about his vision fear of loss is a path to the dark side
highway to the dark side
With that have fun just say no Anakin. I want you to be my representative on the Jedi Council because you are young
So I don't have to pay you work experience Anakin me a Jedi Master
I never said that so he tells the council and they agree that he can't be on the council
But not a Jedi Master. How can I not be a Jedi man?
Damn it, Mindy and the King calm down. It's just a meaningless title being on the council is real power
The reason you can't become master is because age is an important factor
You know wisdom and personal stability May's thought in his head and instead said take a seat
muthafucka Obi explains
they didn't make him master because he's friends with Palpatine and the Jedi want
Separation of church and state but only one way so spy on counselor
Anakin doesn't want to do it because pal P seems like a pretty cool, dude
I agree he meets with Padme who tells him I think the Sith and
Separatists are right tell the counselor but like he gained one powerful friend and now everyone wants favours
Well off to the Opera Anakin have you ever heard the tragedy of Darth Plagueis the wise?
No, well, you could if only an audio book company has sponsored Kilian Darth
Plagueis was a banker who could create life not that impressive with the clones
But he could also force him anywhere to learn this power. Not yet
Well kind of in legend spurts more more speed up healing rave figures out what you were talking about
But her abilities are considered by most to be
enough
Yodas come to Kashyyyk, imagine telling the Kaminoans need three painted uniforms and they'd be like conquer
What's a tree while rookies are dying Yoda isn't a business meeting
Deciding who should fight Grievous while also mocking Ani about fightin is not a master
They send Kenobi to fight Grievous before he lives and it helps him. Sorry for not appreciating your training
Don't worry Anakin. We are not done yet. I didn't teach you how to fight an elevated opponent yet
This is the last time Obi meets Anakin Skywalker the local population tell Obi they are being held hostage
Obi fines Grievous and decides to jump down how suicidal no wonder a knee has saved him so many times
He has the decision-making of a dodo. Hello there
Grievous points out that he has been trained in the Jedi arts by Count Dooku greevey
My boy do the windmill and see what happens. He is useless without the force and runs away
Meanwhile mace tells Annie to report a super generic
Military report to Palpatine and his reaction is apparently going to reveal his intentions
Which is probably gonna be thank you for the report. Please keep me updated
So any ghosts Palpatine high councilor, here's a generic military report Thank You Anakin
I'm the Dark Lord of the Sith
Sidious I want to destroy the Jedi what?
Palpatine is Sidious. Hold on. This is the greatest twist
I actually can't believe it my neurons lack the ability to comprehend this
Got'em, grievous strong
0% body fat total gym goals is is that is more satisfying if you've watched other stuff
Anakin whistle blows to window imagine explaining this to the others that oh, by the way boys were about to fight a Sith Lord
Hope you had your last meal. They go to arrest Palpatine, and he finally reveals his real name
Well, I should go make some coffee. I sure hope I don't miss anything
Through what the hell is the Jedi trying to kill the councilor Anakin this guy with the sword is trying to kill
Poor old man with health problems who can provide green energy with his hands, you know what to do
What have I done?
Miss can be one boring judgmental earring from the council that just pledged myself to your seat teachings
But we have to save Padme to cheat the original trilogy. Only one has mastered me
So, yes, we'll try Darth Sidious
execute order 66
All Jedi's excluding Anakin's are enemies of the Republic
this is way way more brutal if you watch Clone Wars the
Sadness in this see no other media has yet to replicate Dobby gets shot down
You know for the briefest moment, he's probably gonna think this is one of those
Over-ambitious pushing into the pool pranks and he attacks the temple and George is too scared to show him killing children
Now go to the volcano planet and kill all the separatist leaders
Sure, and the King kills everyone accepted techno Union he survives and continues to drop fat bids Canon Obion Yoda
Attack the Jedi Temple and finds out Anakin has rescued the children they kidnapped from a life of servitude
They decide to split up Yoda will take on the Sith Lord
Yoda died then his soul got put into a puppet
That's why he's a puppet in the original movies. Canon Obi follows Padme to meet up with the bad boy
She's ready to forgive him for the child murders and then he strangles her
Beginning to think there might be something off with this relationship, but I don't wanna judge obi-wan
I have to fight you because Williams created an epic battle theme
Oh, yes, it gets absolutely badass battle music. Yes, it will. Absolutely kick your ass
So they fight
I'm a king. Can't you see?
Palpatine is evil I can but I butchered like all the Jedi
Including a lot of children if I surrender
There's gonna be in and out of courtrooms for like the rest of my life gotta convince myself
I was right from my point of view
The Jedi are evil
Obi jumps to the high ground and then points out as Anakin maybe should like find another place to get off and the King
Misunderstands and tell him you are not dealing with the average Jedi warrior
You were supposed to bring balance to the force I did two Jedi to sit
You were supposed to destroy the Sith not join them. I never agreed to that
Smartass aren't you what I'm stealing your lightsaber had mace dying giving birth. Will she make it doctor?
I'm not that kind of doctor robot. I'm a doctor in robot gender studies
So I know maybe she's lost the will to live good guy. Papa Palpatine
Saves Vader and gives him an epic voice to make him less whiny
Okay, Palpatine can't make the dark side look bad. She died of natural causes not related to sit traits like anger
odwin drops off a baby and
Confederacy defeated treacherous religious cult wiped out and peace in the universe
I sure love a happy ending. It ends with them building the Death Star and they used an ancient sea knife
So they they could build sit
The prequels are often bad, but they are never as bad as the ninth film and that's not the Killian experience. That's it
This the experience. Thank you. Please rate five star and favorites
If you're an obsessive Star Wars fan and think I've made an error in this video
Well, I haven't if you're currently under quarantine
Please randomly upload things on my subreddit or slash Killian shorter videos for a while now